

Ádám Novák

28.07.1986. (Hungary)
Reykjavík, Iceland
adamnovak0728@gmail.com
+354 792 2377

I am a hard working individual who has experience working in a variety of settings and from a range of different backgrounds and age groups. Reliable and responsible, I have a keen eye for details and the ability to work accurately under pressure and meet deadlines. I am able to work as part of a team as well as under own initiative.

Work Experience

Date	Job Title	Company	Duties
2020- 2022	Helper on constructions	Various companies (Hungary)	Moving materials, painting, cleaning
Nov 2019 – May 2020	WAREHOUSE MANAGER ASSISTANT	Tentazioni UK Ltd. (London)	Managing pick ticket orders.Pulling items from shelves.Ensuring that orders are accurate.Staging items correctly for delivery. Planning and monitoring product storage. Operating handling equipment etc
March 2019 – Nov 2019	PAISTRY ASSISTANT	The Bread Factory (London)	Prepare baked goods. Fill and decorate paistries and goods. Plate desserts. Monitor supplies. Train new assistants. Present ideas.

Febr 2017 – March 2019	VARIOUS SHORT TERM JOBS	(to improving my language skills after I have came to the UK)	These are: Operative in hand car wash, Recycling operator on a garbage truck, Busser in a night club, Plasterer, Fruit and vegetable packer, Warehouse operative
2015-201 7 / 2011-201 3	TEST TECHNICIAN	Flextronics International Kft. (Budapest)	Maintaining RF based test system, installing product lines, calibrating, training test operators for new processes if required
2013-201 5	DIAGNOSTIC TECHNICIAN / SHIFT LEADER	TMX Mobile Solution Kft. (Budaörs)	Fault finding and repairing smartphones, leading the technicians' team from 2014
2008-201	TRAINER / TEST TECHNICIAN	Jabil Circuit Hungary Kft. (Tiszaújváros)	Organizing and holding general classroom educations for new colleagues, selecting colleagues to assembly processes and teaching them, maintaining, calibrating and installing RF test systems

Education

- Eötvös József Secondary School of Technology equivalent to GCSE
- Windows operating system
- Microsoft Office, Excel, Word, PowerPoint
- Basic knowledge in HTML, CSS and Linux command line

Language Skills

Hungarian ★★★★

 \star

English ★★★